Hey, hey, thanks.
Happy Friday.
I have received your information.
Thank you so much.
This weekend, I have to tell you, as soon as Akashka is here for another four weeks, so to be honest with you, I probably will not even think about that because I want to spend some quality time with her.
Not to mention, she twisted her ankle in the most severe way.
So I'm helping her quite a bit.
And 20 pictures, I have to be honest with you, that's a lot.
I don't have 20 pictures.
I don't normally take pictures of myself.
That's not, it's never been my thing.
Front, back.
And I mean, what you're requesting to me right now is little much.
I'm so sorry.
I'm just being honest.
So eventually at some point, I will look at what I have, but I've never had like full-size pictures front and back.
And I just, it's just, I'm not, I'm not a person that likes to take pictures of myself.
So that's challenging.
And for me to actually spend time doing that, it's just not doesn't make me very happy about it.
So, but listen, I'm all about, I'm really excited to hear about this potential of AI.
And if there's other ways that you can show me its capacity, that would be really lovely.
Maybe we can find another way or maybe we can use somebody else.
That would be great.
Anyway, let me know what you think.
And I will, yeah, I will connect with you shortly.
And then, yeah, I will definitely look at when, like, essentially, time where you can come visit.
With my sister being here, we're all over the place.
Even in her condition, I just want to be one-on-one with her.
And then once she leaves, then I will have my work schedule and then we can collaborate.
Well, obviously, we'll check your schedule, mine, and we'll figure something out.
So, yeah, I have not forgotten about that.
I'm still serious about that.
So, all right, my friend.
In the meantime, keep on smiling.
Take good care.
Take care of yourself in a positive way.
Try to avoid negative self-talks and do things that make you happy on a daily basis.
All right.
Take care of yourself.
Okay, Pa.