I was alone in the office elevator, heading down after a long day.
Just as the doors were closing, a hand shot through.
An older man in a gray suit jumped in, smiling politely.
We descended in silence until the lights flickered and the elevator jerked to a stop.
I sighed, thinking great, just my luck.
The man calmly pressed the emergency button.
I tried making small talk to break the tension.
He nodded, but didn't say much.
Just stood there quickly, hands folded.
Or quietly, not messing all up.
Minutes later, the elevator resumed.
As we reached the ground floor, he turned to me and said, thanks for the company.
Not many people talk to me anymore.
I smiled awkwardly, but when I looked back as he walked away, he was gone.
And the security guard said no one had entered the building in hours.